You need to learn MCP right now. MCP
你现在就需要学习MCP。  MCP
makes AI do things overpowered things.
使 AI 能够执行一些过于强大的操作。
Like when I connected Claude to my
就像我把克劳德连接到我的
Obsidian vault. What? Or Brave or Kali
黑曜石金库时那样。 什么？ 或者 Brave 或 Kali
Linux? My jaw dropped. I mean, look at
Linux？ 我惊得下巴都快掉下来了。 我的意思是，看看
this. Claude is hacking with Kali Linux
这个。  Claude 现在正在用 Kali Linux 进行黑客攻击
right now. So, in this video, I'm going
。 那么，在这个视频中，我将向
to show you the magic of the model
你展示模型
context protocol. I'll break down what
上下文协议的神奇之处。 我会详细解释它
it is, show you how to use it with
是什么，并向您展示如何将其与
Docker containers. It's all local, and
Docker 容器一起使用。 所有内容都是本地化的，甚至包括
even how to build your very own custom
如何为你能想到的任何用途构建你自己的自定义
MCP servers for literally anything you
MCP 服务器
can think of. My goal by the end of this
。 本
video is to create a Kali Linux MCP
视频的目标是创建一个 Kali Linux MCP
server so our LLMs can hack for us.
服务器，以便我们的 LLM 可以为我们进行黑客攻击。
Doesn't that sound awesome? Get your
听起来是不是很棒？ 准备好你的
coffee ready. Let's go.
咖啡。 我们走吧。
And shout out to Docker for making this
还要感谢 Docker，是他们的支持才使得这段
video possible. So, giving LLM access to
视频得以制作完成。 因此，让LLM访问
our tools makes them insanely powerful
我们的工具会使它们变得非常强大，
and it's necessary if we want them to do
如果我们想让它们做任何有意义的事情，这是必要的
anything productive. But to do this is
。 但这样做
kind of hard. And I hate to say this,
有点难。 我很不想这么说，
but you have to think about LM like
但你必须在某种程度上把LM（可能是指某个角色或组织）看作是
people to a point. Now, for us humans,
人。 对于我们人类来说，
when we want to use tools like a task
当我们想要使用任务
manager or an email manager, we're not
管理器或电子邮件管理器之类的工具时，我们不会
going to be interacting with the code,
与代码进行交互，
right? No, no one would use it. That's
对吧？ 不，没人会用它。 这就是
why we have user interfaces or guies.
为什么我们需要用户界面或图形用户界面（GUI）。
This nice, friendly interface abstracts
这种友好简洁的界面抽象化
away the complicated code, making it
了复杂的代码，使
easier and possible for most humans to
大多数人都能更轻松地
use it. Solution found. Let's just give
使用它。 问题已解决。 咱们就给
the LLM a guey. They'll love it. No,
法学硕士学位打个折扣吧。 他们一定会喜欢的。 不，
they won't. They hate gooies. At least
他们不会。 他们讨厌黏糊糊的东西。 至少
for now. LLMs, they love text. So giving
目前是这样。 法学硕士们，他们喜欢文字。 所以给
them a gooey, it's like they can do it.
他们一些黏糊糊的东西，他们就好像能做到一样。
It's hard. It takes forever. Okay, fine.
这很难。 真是太费时间了。 好吧，行。
Just give them the code. LLMs love code,
直接把代码给他们就行了。 法学硕士都喜欢编程，
right? Not going to work. They need
对吧？ 行不通。 他们需要
access to that code and your apps are
访问那段代码，而你的应用
not going to give it. But hold up. What
不会提供这种访问权限。 等等。
about APIs? That would be perfect,
API方面呢？ 那岂不是完美了
right? Application programming
？ 应用程序编程
interfaces were built so that one
接口的构建是为了使一个
program could use the tools of another
程序能够使用另一个程序的工具
program. You can't give a program a
。 你不能给程序一个
guey, but you can expose API endpoints
guey，但你可以公开 API 端点，
that allow a program to programmatically
使程序能够以
use these tools in a language it
它能理解的语言以编程方式使用这些工具
understands. So, for example, my real
。 例如，我实际使用的
task manager, ClickUp, they expose an
任务管理软件 ClickUp，它公开了一个
API endpoint that allows a program to
API 端点，允许程序
create a task for you. And when I
为你创建一个任务。 当我
pretend to be a program, watch what
假装成一个程序时，看看会
happens. Boom. Task comes in. Or I can
发生什么。 繁荣。 任务来了。或者我可以
use the Obsidian REST API, pretend to be
使用 Obsidian REST API，假装成
a computer, and create a new note. How
一台电脑，创建一个新笔记。
cool is that? So, what's the point of
这也太酷了吧？ 那么，这段视频的意义何在
this video? Problem solved. Give the LLM
？ 问题解决了。 授予LLM
API access. Hold on. Let's say we did.
API访问权限。 坚持，稍等。 假设我们真的这么做了。
First of all, this API stuff, that's
首先，这些 API 相关的东西，其实就是
code. in order to interact with the API
代码。 为了与 API 端点进行交互
endpoints. That's going to be running
。 那将会运行
some sort of code, which the LLMs often
一些代码，而LLM通常
don't have access to. And even if they
没有权限访问这些代码。 即使他们真的这么做了
did, look at this API documentation. I
，也请看看这份 API 文档。 我的
mean, look at ClickUps. It's super
意思是，看看ClickUps就知道了。 太
intense. You'd have to code each one of
刺激了。 你需要编写每个
those API interactions and instruct the
API 交互的代码，并指导
LLM on how to do it. Now, don't get me
LLM 如何执行这些操作。 别误会我的意思
wrong, people do this and it works, but
，有人这样做，而且也确实有效，但这
it's kind of a pain, right? And there's
有点麻烦，对吧？ 而且
no standard way to do it. There's got to
没有标准的做法。 肯定有更
be an easier way, right? Check the title
简单的办法，对吧？ 请查看
of the video. MCP came in to save the
视频标题。  MCP及时出现，力挽狂澜
day. MCP is the model context protocol,
。  MCP 是模型上下文协议，是
a standardized way to give tools to LLM.
一种为 LLM 提供工具的标准化方法。
It's kind of like how USBC solved our
这有点像 USB-C 解决了我们的
cable issues. Created by Anthropic, it
线缆问题。 这款产品由 Anthropic 公司研发，
did not take long for this to become the
很快就成为了
industry standard. And here's why. Check
行业标准。 原因如下。 看看
this out. So, instead of the LLM having
这个。 因此，LLM
to run code to interact with the APIs,
无需运行代码来与 API 交互，
we'll throw in what's called an MCP
我们将引入一个称为 MCP
server. This server is abstracting away
服务器的东西。 该服务器将
all the complexity of these API calls.
所有API调用的复杂性都抽象化了。
Now, what does that mean? It means all
那么，这意味着什么呢？ 这意味着
the code that you would normally have to
通常需要
write to interact with the API, the MCP
编写的所有与 API 交互的代码，MCP
server is handling that. It has that
服务器都会处理。 它
written into its code. It'll do all that
的代码里已经写入了这一点。 它会
for you or for the LLM. So, all we have
为你或法学硕士课程完成所有这些工作。 所以，我们只需
to do is say, "Hey LLM, connect to this
要说：“嘿 LLM，连接到这个
MCP server." Slot right in. We'll say,
MCP 服务器。” 直接插入即可。我们会说：
"Hey, Mr. AI, when you want to create a
“嘿，人工智能先生，当您想要创建
task or get a task, you don't have to
任务或获取任务时，您无需
code anything. Just simply ask the MCP
编写任何代码。只需简单地请求 MCP
server to do it." The MCP server will
服务器来完成即可。”  MCP 服务器会
have these tasks or tools exposed like
公开这些任务或工具，例如
create a task and all the LLM has to do
创建任务，而 LLM 只需
is simply ask and use that task. It
请求并使用该任务即可。 它
doesn't have to know anything about API
不需要了解任何关于 API
endpoints, anything about the code,
端点、代码、
authentication, none of that. The MCP
身份验证之类的东西。  MCP
server abstracts all that complexity and
服务器抽象化了所有这些复杂性，使
makes it kind of stupid simple for our
我们的
AI. We essentially created a guey for
AI 能够以极其简单的方式进行操作。 我们基本上为
our LLM. They just have to click a
我们的法学硕士课程创建了一个团队。 他们只需要点击一个
button. And the most exciting part about
按钮。 而最令人兴奋的
this is that this MCP thing is now the
是，MCP现在已经成为
standard. So if your AI, if your LLM has
标准了。 因此，如果你的 AI，如果你的 LLM 能够
the ability to connect to an MCP server,
连接到 MCP 服务器（
which most do now, everyone's adopting
现在大多数 AI 都能够做到这一点），那么每个人都在采用
it. Then you can connect to a ton of
它。 这样你就可以连接到大量的
applications because everyone's exposing
应用程序，因为每个人都
their APIs via an MCP server. Enough
通过 MCP 服务器公开他们的 API。 够了，别再
talking about it. Let's have you try an
说了。 现在就让您试用一下
MCP server right now. Quick sip of
MCP 服务器。 快速喝一口
coffee.
咖啡。
Let's get you connected to one. I just
我们帮你联系一个。 我刚把
heated up my coffee. It's super hot.
咖啡热了一下。 天气超级热。
Now, I've got good news. It's actually
现在，我有个好消息。 实际上，
right now locally on your computer. Let
现在在你的电脑本地运行自己的 MCP 服务器非常简单。 让
me show you. It's going to be using
我来给你演示一下。 它将使用
Docker. Shocker. That rhymed. And you
Docker。 令人震惊。 押韵了。 而且你
can do this on pretty much any machine
几乎可以在任何你想要的机器上做到这一点
you want. Mac, Linux, Windows. The one
。  Mac、Linux、Windows。 唯一的
requirement is that you're running
要求是您必须运行
Docker Desktop. Actually, let me do a
Docker Desktop。 实际上，让我
whole what you need thing real quick.
快速地完成你需要的一切。
I'm not sure why I did jazz hands there.
我也不知道当时为什么会做出爵士手势。
That felt very weird. I can't imagine
感觉很奇怪。 我无法想象
how it felt for you. So, Docker Desktop
你当时的感受。 所以，
and you'll also need an LLM app,
你需要 Docker Desktop，还需要一个 LLM 应用，
something that can run large language
一个能够运行大型语言
models and something that can use MCP
模型并且能够使用 MCP
servers. I'm going to demonstrate three
服务器的应用。 我将演示三种
options. I'll show you cloud desktop, my
方案。 我将向您展示云桌面，这是我
personal favorite. It's free. This will
个人最喜欢的。 它是免费的。 这将
be using the cloud models, which are
使用云模型，这些模型
fantastic. I'll show you LM Studio for
非常棒。 我将向您展示 LM Studio，它适用于像
local models like Llama. And for all you
Llama 这样的本地模型。 对于所有
people who love, I'll show you Cursor.
热爱音乐的人，我将向你们展示 Cursor。
Let's get started with our Docker
让我们开始
desktop install. It's really easy. I've
安装 Docker Desktop 吧。 这很简单。 我
got a fresh Mac here. I'm going to go
这里有一台全新的Mac电脑。 我要去访问
out to docs.docker.com.
docs.docker.com。
docker.com/destop
docker.com/destop，就这些了
and that's it. I'll have all the links
。 我会
below in a guide. For me, I'll do Docker
在下面的指南中列出所有链接。 对我来说，我会
Desktop on Apple Silicon. I'm not going
在 Apple Silicon 上运行 Docker Desktop。 我不会详细讲解
to walk through Windows or Linux
Windows 或 Linux 的
installs, but they'll all be below. Keep
安装过程，但所有步骤都会在下面列出。 请
in mind, Windows does involve the extra
注意，Windows 系统需要额外
step of getting WSL 2 or HyperV set up
设置 WSL 2 或 HyperV
as a backend. We're not going to cover
作为后端。 这里我们就不赘述了
that here, but there are docs in the
，但下面的描述中有相关文档
description below. All right, I'll go
。 好的，我这就去
ahead and install Docker Desktop and
安装 Docker Desktop，
then launch it. We'll sign our life away
然后启动它。 我们
by accepting all terms. Use recommended
接受所有条款，就等于把自己的人生出卖给了别人。 使用推荐
settings. And now here, you can create a
设置。 现在，您可以在这里创建
Docker login if you want. You don't have
Docker 登录帐户（如果需要）。 你不一定
to, but I recommend it. It's free. No
要这样做，但我建议你这样做。 它是免费的。 别有
pressure. Now, Docker Desktop is great
压力。 现在，Docker Desktop 非常擅长
at running Docker containers. You
运行 Docker 容器。 你
probably saw that coming, but maybe what
可能已经预料到了，但
you didn't see coming is they're great
你或许没想到的是，他们非常擅长使用
at running MCP servers with their MCP
MCP 工具包运行 MCP 服务器
toolkit. This is brand new, hot off the
。 这是最新推出的，新鲜出炉的
presses. And when I first heard about
。 当我第一次听到
it, I didn't care so much. Honestly, I'm
这件事的时候，我并不太在意。 说实话，我
like, so what? Then I tried it. And now
心想，那又怎样？ 然后我试了一下。 而现在
I use it every single stinking day. It's
我每天都用它。
amazing. Now, to get this working, we
太神奇了。 要让它正常工作，我们
have to turn on a few things. The main
需要开启一些功能。 最重要的
thing is the MCP toolkit. We'll click on
是MCP工具包。 我们马上点击一下
that real quick. Actually, is it already
。 实际上，它已经
installed and set up? Let's go make
安装设置好了吗？ 我们去
sure. Let's go to our settings. We'll go
确认一下。 让我们进入设置页面。 我们将
to beta features. Okay, I already had
启用测试版功能。 好的，我已经
Docker MCP toolkit enabled. Go check
启用了 Docker MCP 工具包。
there right now to make sure you don't
现在就去那里查看一下，确保你
already have it enabled. And that's um
还没有启用它。 这就是
all we had to do. Now, let's pick an MCP
我们所要做的全部工作。 现在，让我们选择一个 MCP
server to run. They have a whole
服务器来运行。 他们有全套产品
catalog. Look at all this. Now, these
目录。 看看这一切。 这些
are official MCP servers that are part
是MCP官方服务器，属于
of their catalog. As I mentioned, we can
他们的产品目录。 正如我之前提到的，我们可以自己
make our own. I'll show you that here in
制作。 我马上就给你看
a moment. But let's search for one that
。 但我们还是找个
will be really fun right now. Obsidian.
现在就能玩得开心的游戏吧。 黑曜石。   是的
So, yes, there is an Obsidian MCP
，确实存在 Obsidian MCP
server. I'll just add the sucker. And
服务器。 我只要把那个吸盘加进去就行了。
all I have to do is paste in my Obsidian
我只需要粘贴我的 Obsidian
API key, which I can get from Obsidian
API 密钥，我可以从 Obsidian 网站获取该密钥
here. Now, Obsidian is a local open-
。  Obsidian 是一款本地
source notes application, my favorite. I
开源笔记应用程序，也是我最喜欢的。 我
use it every day. And they have a
每天都用它。 他们还有一个
community plugin called local REST API
名为本地 REST API 的社区插件，
that I installed. We already used it
我已经安装了。 我们之前已经用过了
earlier. I'm going to grab this API key
。 我将获取它提供的这个 API 密钥，
that it provides and paste it into this
并将其粘贴到这里的
field here.
字段中。   就这样。
And that's it. Getting back to my
回到我的
servers tab here. You can see I have an
服务器选项卡。 您可以看到我有一个
Obsidian server, 12 tools available. If
Obsidian 服务器，有 12 个工具可用。 如果
I jump in there, I can see what the
我进去看看，就能知道有哪些
tools are. Click on tools and you can
工具了。 点击工具，您可以
see that it's describing these tools in
看到它用通俗易懂的语言描述了这些工具
plain language. Use Obsidian append
。 使用 Obsidian 追加
content to append content to a new or
内容功能，可以将内容追加到
existing file in the vault. Behind the
Vault 中的新文件或现有文件中。 在
scenes, it's doing all these API calls
后台，它一直在
to the Obsidian REST API. But for you,
向 Obsidian REST API 发出各种 API 调用。 但对于你、
me, and the LLM, we just know we say,
我以及法学硕士来说，我们只知道我们会说：
"Hey, get some changes. Hey, do a simple
“嘿，做些修改。嘿，做个简单的
search." And it does it for you. You
搜索。” 它会为你自动完成这一切。 你
ready to see it happen? Now, you're
准备好见证这一切了吗？ 接下来，您
about to see some slide of hand here.
将看到一些手部动作。
Really just some magic behind the
其实幕后有一些魔法
scenes. Something absolutely crazy is
。 发生一件非常疯狂的事情
happening. Something called the Docker
。 一个叫做 Docker
MCP gateway. Okay, I'm not going to show
MCP 网关的东西。 好吧，我暂时还不给
you that just yet. We'll cover more on
你们看。 我们稍后会详细介绍
that later, but just know it's doing
，但你只需要知道它
some extra magic behind the scenes. Now,
在幕后发挥了一些额外的神奇作用。 现在，
notice under MCP toolkit, we have the
请注意 MCP 工具包，我们有
option for servers, the catalog, and
服务器选项、目录选项，
then we have clients. These are the LLMs
然后还有客户端选项。 这些是
that can interact with the Docker MCP
能够与 Docker MCP
servers. Look at that. Cloud desktop is
服务器交互的 LLM。 瞧瞧。 云桌面就在
right here. What do you say we connect?
这里。 不如我们联系一下？   事情就是这样。
And that was it. I just did it. So, I
我刚刚就这么做了。 所以，我
have Cloud running right now. This is a
现在已经启动了云服务。 这是一个
free account. I don't pay for anything.
免费账户。 我什么都不用付钱。
I'm going to restart it. Launch it
我打算重新启动它。 再次启动它
again. And by the way, ignore this. We
。 顺便说一句，忽略这条信息。 有了我们
won't need this right now with our own
自己的定制工具，目前我们还不需要这个
custom tools. Now, I'm going to click on
。 现在，我要点击
this setting box right here. And you're
这里的设置框。 你
gonna see something amazing. MCP Docker.
将会看到令人惊叹的事情。  MCP Docker。
That's us. That's what we just did. If I
那就是我们。 我们刚才就是这么做的。 如果我
click on that, it's going to show you
点击它，就会显示我们
the tools that we just added to Claude.
刚刚添加到 Claude 中的工具。
So, watch this. Yo, create a note in my
所以，请看好这个。 嘿，在我的 Obsidian 里创建一个笔记，
Obsidian detailing the best way to make
详细说明制作
French press coffee. Let's go. Now, it's
法压咖啡的最佳方法。 我们走吧。 现在，它要
going to start thinking. Then it's going
开始思考了。 然后它就会
to realize, oh, I have a tool available
意识到，哦，我有一个工具可以使用
to me. I'm going to try and use that.
。 我打算试试看。
Let's look behind the scenes here. Yeah,
让我们来看看幕后情况。 是的，
it's getting it ready now. It's going to
它正在准备中。 它会
ask you permission to use that tool
请求您允许使用该工具，
because it is accessing things outside
因为它正在访问超出
of its normal purview. Sure, I will
其正常权限范围的内容。 当然，这次我就
allow it just this one time, though.
允许一次。
Okay, so it said it did it. Let's go
好的，它说它已经完成了。 我们去看
take a look.
看吧。
There it is in my notes. Are you
我的笔记里有。 你他妈在
stinking kidding me? H, it works the
开玩笑吧？  H，
same way for search. I'm going to create
搜索也是同样的原理。 我打算在
a fun note here. Just something random.
这里写个有趣的小笔记。 随便说说。
Cool. Now I'm going to ask it to search.
凉爽的。 现在我要让它进行搜索。
Hey, search my vault for something about
嘿，帮我翻翻我的资料库，找找关于
drinking tea. I'll allow one time to do
喝茶的资料。 我会允许你进行一次
the simple search.
简单的搜索。
It's going to do a broader search. It'll
它将进行更广泛的搜索。 它会
try a few times. It's going to read the
尝试几次。 它将读取
note or get the file contents. But see,
笔记或获取文件内容。 但是，你看，
here's what's happening here. This is
这里发生的事情是这样的。 这就是
why this is amazing. It's not having to
它令人惊叹之处。 不需要进行
authenticate. Doesn't know anything
身份验证。 他对此一无所知
about that. Doesn't care. Doesn't know
。 不在乎。 完全不懂
any code or API, anything at all. It
代码或API，一窍不通。 它只
just knows that it can call that tool,
知道它可以调用那个工具，
use that task tool, and that's it. And I
使用那个任务工具，仅此而已。 我
got the information. This is so powerful
得到了相关信息。 这
for us. Are you kidding me? Coffee break
对我们来说意义非凡。 你在开玩笑吧？ 休息一下喝杯咖啡吧
for that.
。
Hey, never chat from the future here.
嘿，千万别在这里从未来视角聊天。
What I'm showing you here, it's cool,
我在这里展示的东西很酷，
but it's all local. At this time stamp,
但都是本地的。 从那时起，
I'm going to show you the Docker MCP
我将向大家展示 Docker MCP
gateway and how we can make any tool you
网关，以及如何让您构建的任何工具可以
build remotely accessible from things
从诸如 N8N 之类的设备远程访问
like, I don't know, N8N. Dude, it's so
。 老兄，这太
cool. I'll see you there. Back to the
酷了。 到时候见。 回到
video. I seriously have goosebumps just
视频。 光是
talking about this. And I've been using
说起这件事，我就起鸡皮疙瘩了。 我已经用了好
this for a minute now. What do you say
一会儿了。 不如
we go add a few more MCP servers?
我们再增加几台MCP服务器？
Because we can add a lot. We can go
因为我们可以添加很多东西。 我们可能会
crazy. Let's go to the catalog. duck.go.
疯掉。 我们去看看产品目录吧。  duck.go。
Sure, I want one. It's already there.
当然，我也想要一个。 它已经在那里了。
Fetch. It'll grab URLs. Got it. Or it'll
拿来。 它会抓取网址。 知道了。 或者，它会
grab the contents of a website given a
根据网址抓取网站内容
URL. Oh, they have so many cool ones.
。 哦，他们有很多很酷的款式。
Oh, they have Brave search. I need an
哦，他们有Brave搜索功能。 我需要一个
API key. I don't feel like getting that
API密钥。 我现在没心情去拿那个
right now. Oo, Airbnb search. Let's do
。 哦，Airbnb 搜索。 那就
that. Ooh, YouTube transcripts. We can
这么做吧。 哦，YouTube 文字稿。 我们可以
do that. That's crazy. Okay, let's try
做到。 太疯狂了。 好的，我们来
it out. Now, this time I'm going to add
试一试。 这次我打算再增加
some more clients. Let's add um cursor.
一些客户。 我们来添加光标。
Click connect. Done. LM Studio. Click
点击连接。 完毕。  LM工作室。 点击
connect. Done. Now, it's that easy
连接。 完毕。 现在就这么简单，
because I already have cursor in LM
因为我已经为 LM
Studio installed. And behind the scenes,
Studio 安装了光标插件。 而实际上，
all it's doing is updating an MCP server
它所做的只是更新
config file that each one of these apps
每个应用程序都有一个 MCP 服务器配置文件
has. Now, let's try LM Studio. I'm going
。 现在，我们来试试LM Studio。 我打算
to restart it real quick to make sure
快速重启一下，确保
I've got everything I need. And LM
我需要的所有东西都已准备就绪。  LM
Studio again is what we can use to run
Studio 仍然是我们可以用来运行
local um LLMs. I'll load a model. We'll
本地 LLM 的工具。 我将加载一个模型。 我们将
do Gemma 312B. And then I think I'll go
做 Gemma 312B。 然后我想我会下去
down here to my plug and see. Oh, yep.
看看我的插座。 哦，是的。
There it is. We'll connect our MCP
找到了。 我们将连接我们的MCP
tools. MCP Docker sitting right there.
工具。  MCP Docker 就在那里。
If I click that tool icon, we can see
如果我点击那个工具图标，我想我们就能看到
all the tools, I think. Oh, yeah. There
所有的工具了。 哦，是的。 找到了
it is. Beautiful. Now, let's ask it to
。 美丽的。 现在，我们让它
do something. So, I'll say, "Find the
做点什么。 所以，我会说：“找出
Dallas. Use the dot.go tool and then
达拉斯排名前十的日本餐厅。使用 dot.go 工具，然后
findings using the Obsidian tool. Local
用 Obsidian 工具在我的资料库里创建一份包含你发现的笔记。本地化
model. Let's see how you do, buddy."
模式。看看你做得怎么样，伙计。”
Keep in mind, these MCP servers are
请注意，这些 MCP 服务器是在
running locally on my computer. I'll
我的本地计算机上运行的。 我会
give it permission. Go ahead, bud. Okay.
批准的。 去吧，伙计。 好的。
But it didn't create the note in my
但它并没有在我的保险库中创建该记录
vault. Let's try it again. Okay. Gemma's
。 我们再试一次。 好的。 杰玛
kind of dumb. Let's try DeepSeek, a
有点笨。 我们来试试DeepSeek，一个
model that can think.
能够思考的模型。
Give her permission. Come on, buddy. You
允许她这样做。 来吧，伙计。 你
can do this. All right. Gave permission
可以做到。 好的。 已授权
to Obsidian. Okay. It found the Japanese
给 Obsidian。 好的。 它找到了日本
restaurants. Let's check Obsidian. It
餐馆。 我们来看看黑曜石。 成功了
did it. Oh no.
。 哦，不。
Local models are dumb. But it did the
本地模型很笨。 但它确实
tool call, which is what we cared about.
调用了工具，这正是我们所关心的。
If we did that same thing in Claude, it
如果我们对克劳德也这样做，
would move very quickly.
进展会非常快。
[Music]
[音乐]
Okay. Said I did it. Let's check it out.
好的。 我说是我做的。 我们来看看。
Oh, I did a great job. Check that out.
哦，我做得非常棒。 看看这个。
That's so fun. Let's see if Cursor can
真有趣。 我们来看看 Cursor 能否
do the same thing. I'm going to restart
做到同样的事情。 我要重启
Cursor.
Cursor 程序。
Grab the transcript
获取
for this YouTube video. Look at that.
此 YouTube 视频的文字稿。 瞧瞧。
Run the tool. And this is the free
运行该工具。 而且这还是
version of Cursor, too. Oh my gosh, it
Cursor 的免费版本。 我的天哪，它
grabbed it. Now, let's add that to my
抓住了它。 现在，让我们把它添加到我的
Obsidian Vault. It's so powerful, man.
黑曜石宝库中。 它威力太大了，伙计。
Okay, it finished. Let's go check our
好了，结束了。 我们去看看
note. There it is. Grabbed my YouTube
笔记吧。 找到了。 我找到了我的 YouTube
video, summarized it, put it in our
视频，做了个总结，然后把它写进了我们的
note. Come on. Are you not excited about
笔记里。 快点。 你难道不期待
that coffee stinking break?
那场咖啡味十足的休息吗？
You know, people ask me, "Is that
你知道，人们经常问我：“那是
enthusiasm? Is that fake? Is that
热情吗？那是装出来的吗？那是事先
scripted?" No, it's not. Ask my wife.
写好的剧本吗？” 不，不是。 问问我老婆。
I'm always like this. All right, here we
我一直都是这样。 好了，我们开始吧
go. It's time for you to build your very
。 是时候搭建你
own MCP server. Custom, just how you
自己的MCP服务器了。 完全定制，按照您的
want it. Because there may not be an MCP
意愿打造。 因为可能没有一款 MCP
server out there that does what you want
服务器能够满足您的需求
it to do. So, right now, I'm going to
。 所以，现在我将一
walk you through building three MCP
步步指导大家搭建三台 MCP
servers. Yeah, three. Because it's kind
服务器。 对，三个。 因为这很
of easy. I did a lot of work to figure
容易。 我做了很多工作才
out how to make this work well. I went
弄明白如何才能让它顺利运行。 我为了
through the pain for you. The first one
你承受了痛苦。 第一个演示
will be a fun demo, a simple dice roller
将是一个有趣的演示，一个简单的掷骰子程序，
just to kick the tires, make sure things
只是为了测试一下，确保一切
are working. Then I'll show you how to
正常。 接下来，我将向你展示如何
build some real tools involving APIs.
构建一些涉及 API 的实际工具。
But seriously, you're going to feel like
但说真的，
you can do anything after learning how
学会这个之后，你会觉得自己无所不能
to do this. The world we're living in
。 我们现在生活的世界太
right now is crazy. Let's get started.
疯狂了。 我们开始吧。
Now, the secret sauce behind all this is
这一切背后的秘诀就是
this prompt that I built. Here it is.
我创建的这个提示。 这里是。
Network Chuck's MCP server build prompt.
网络查克的 MCP 服务器构建提示。
contained in this one prompt is
这一条提示包含了
everything an AI will need to build you
人工智能构建
an MCP server. All you have to do is
MCP 服务器所需的一切信息。 你只需要
describe what you want. Let's do it
描述一下你想要什么。 我们
right now. By the way, if you don't want
现在就做。 顺便说一下，如果您
to run all this LLM stuff right now, I
现在不想运行所有这些 LLM 相关的东西，我
do have this entire example in my GitHub
的 GitHub 链接里有完整的示例
link right here. Just around maybe here,
。 大概就在这儿，
we'll tell it something. Okay, I want to
我们会告诉它一些事情。 好的，我想
build a very simple dice roller MCP
搭建一个非常简单的骰子滚动 MCP
server. I wanted to do coin flips, DND
服务器。 我想做抛硬币、龙与地下城之类的
stuff, any kind of dice roller mechanic.
游戏，任何类型的掷骰子机制。
Bake that in, make it simple and clean.
把这些想法融入其中，让它变得简单干净。
Let's copy and paste this whole thing.
我们把这段内容全部复制粘贴过来。
Pick an LLM that you know is pretty good
选择一位你认为编程能力很强的法学硕士
at coding. Your quality will vary. I
。 质量会有差异。 我
right now love Claude Opus 41. He's kind
现在特别喜欢克劳德·奥普斯41。他简直
of amazing. Just going to paste this in
太棒了。 我就把这段粘贴进去就
and go. Coffee break while AI makes
行了。 趁着人工智能创造
magic things happen. And what this will
奇迹的空档，喝杯咖啡吧。 它会
spit out is everything you need to build
输出构建
this server. It'll walk you through it
此服务器所需的一切。 它会一步一步地引导你完成操作
step by step. I think I asked it to do
。 我觉得我让它做的
too many things.
事情太多了。
It's almost done. Okay, it finally
快完成了。 好了，终于
finished. It gave us a lot of stuff and
结束了。 它给了我们很多东西，
we're going to follow it step by step.
我们将一步一步地按照它来做。
Now, it created us five files. A Docker
现在，它为我们创建了五个文件。  Docker
file, requirements, dice server, readin,
文件、需求、Dice 服务器、读取
and a cloud. MD file. You really only
和云。  MD文件。
need the first four unless you're using
除非你用的是凝血剂，否则你其实只需要前四种就够了
clot. And all the files should be right
。 所有文件都应该在
above it here. So, first I'll create a
它上面。 首先，我要创建一个
directory. Call it my dice or something.
目录。 叫它我的骰子之类的吧。
I don't know, something stupid. Jump in
我不知道，大概是做了什么蠢事吧。 进去吧
there. cd my dice. And we'll create our
。 把骰子刻成光盘。 接下来，我们将
Docker file real quick. I'm just going
快速创建 Docker 文件。 我打算直接用
to PB paste that in there. It's a
PB 粘贴进去。 这是
special thing on Mac.
Mac上的特殊之处。
The Docker file will describe how to
Docker 文件将描述如何
build a Docker container, which we're
构建 Docker 容器，我们接下来就
about to do. We'll then do the
要这样做。 接下来我们将编写
requirements file, which is almost
需求文件，这部分内容几乎可以忽略
nothing. Requirements.txt
不计。  requirements.txt 文件，
and then the server, which will be the
然后是服务器，服务器将是
biggest piece of this.
其中最重要的部分。
dice_server.py.
dice_server.py。
And by the way, to create these files in
顺便说一句，要在命令行创建这些文件
the command line, you can use nano them,
，你可以使用 nano 编辑器，
I don't care. And then finally, the
我不在乎。 最后，还有
readme file, which is just nice to have.
readme 文件，有它就更好了。
Now, that's all we really need to do
现在，我们只需要这些就能完成
this. We're going to run one command
这件事了。 我们现在要运行一条命令
right now. We'll follow the instructions
。 我们将按照这里的指示操作
here. Yep, right here. Docker build.
。 没错，就是这里。  Docker 构建。   把
Paste that in. And it's going to build a
这段文字粘贴进去。它现在就会创建一个
Docker container right now. Quick coffee
Docker 容器。 短暂
break.
休息，喝杯咖啡。
And what it's doing, if you're not
如果你不
familiar with this, is it's taking all
熟悉这个，它的作用是获取所有
that stuff, the Docker file, which
那些东西，也就是 Docker 文件，它
describes how to build the Docker
描述了如何构建 Docker
container. It's going to add our Python
容器。 它将添加我们的Python
server config. And it's done. If we type
服务器配置。 搞定了。 如果我们
in Docker image ls, we'll see our DICE
输入 Docker 镜像 ls，就会看到我们的 DICE
MCP server right there along with our
MCP 服务器以及
other MCP servers that we added through
我们通过 Docker 目录添加的其他 MCP 服务器
the Docker catalog. Speaking of catalog,
。 说到产品目录，
we need to make our own. Now, see here
我们需要自己制作一个。 现在，请看这里的
in the instructions, they say you can
说明，上面说
make a catalog directory if you don't
如果您
already have one. You probably already
还没有目录，可以创建一个。 你可能已经
have one. And if we type in ls do our
有一个了。 如果我们输入 ls 命令，我们的
home directory look in Docker the Docker
主目录将在 Docker
directory. It's hidden inside MCP and
目录中查找。 它隐藏在 MCP 和
cataloges. See I already have a few here
产品目录中。 你看，我这里已经有几个了，它们就待在这里
just kind of chilling out. If you just
放松一下。 如果你只
install this you'll just see
安装这个，你只会看到
dockermcp.yaml.
dockermcp.yaml 文件。
We're going to make our own right now.
我们现在就要自己动手做。
Your AI prompt should spit out a custom
您的 AI 提示符应该输出自定义
YAML. We'll grab that. We'll create our
YAML 文件。 我们会拿走它。 我们将
own right now in that location.
立即在该地点创建我们自己的版本。
Docker MCP cataloges. I'll call it my
Docker MCP 目录。 我把它叫做我的
custom catalog.
定制产品目录。
Done. And there's one more thing we have
完毕。 还有一件事我们必须
to do and it's going to tell us right
做，它马上就会告诉我们
here. We need to edit the registry. Now,
。 我们需要编辑注册表。 现在，
this is how the Docker MCP gateway is
Docker MCP 网关的
going to work. Docker has their built-in
工作原理如下。  Docker 有自己的内置
catalog. You can also add custom
目录。 您还可以
cataloges like this or like this. And
像这样或像这样添加自定义目录。
that's just a catalog. Like you shop for
那只是个产品目录而已。 就像你选购要
the MCP server you want to add. Once you
添加的 MCP 服务器一样。
do add them, they get added to what's
添加完成后，它们会被添加到
called the registry, which if I ls
所谓的注册表中。如果我 ls
the Docker MCP directory, you can see
Docker MCP 目录，可以看到
the registry file is right there.
注册表文件就在那里。
registry.yaml. Let's look inside that
registry.yaml。 我们快速看一下里面的情况
real quick.
。
And there is simply a reference to our
这里只是提到了我们
installed servers. And it's when you
已安装的服务器。 只有当你
actually install it and register it that
实际安装并注册后，
it shows up here. Now, we're not going
它才会出现在这里。 现在，我们
to be able to do that through the guey.
无法通过 guey 做到这一点。
So, we have to add ours manually here.
所以，我们需要在这里手动添加。
It's actually pretty easy. We're going
其实很简单。 我们将
to do nano or whatever you want to use
使用 nano 或其他你喜欢的编辑器
to edit this file. And at the very
来编辑这个文件。
bottom, using the same format, keeping
最后，我们将采用相同的格式，保持
everything lined up, we will add our
所有内容排列整齐，添加我们的
server. It's called dice according to my
服务器。 根据我的提示，它叫做骰子
prompt here. And we put that ref thing.
。 我们把那个参考点放进去了。
Crl + xy. Enter to save. That's all we
Crl + xy。 输入保存。 这就是我们唯一
got to worry about. And let me tell you,
需要担心的事。 我告诉你，
uh, we're almost done. I was going to
呃，我们快完成了。 我本来
say we're done, but we're not done yet.
想说我们结束了，但其实还没结束。
We do need to edit our cloud MCP server
我们需要修改云端MCP服务器
config. We're going to change it to look
配置。 我们将把它改成类似这样的样子
something like this. I'm just going to
。 我直接
copy this and paste it into my cloud
复制粘贴这段代码到我的云
config here. And there's a few things
配置里就行了。 现在有几件事正在
happening. Notice it's still running the
发生。 请注意，它仍在运行
Docker MCP gateway command. It's just
Docker MCP 网关命令。 它只是
running a few more options. And I
运行了一些额外的选项。
actually need to change two things here.
实际上，我需要在这里修改两处地方。
First, I'll need to make sure I change
首先，我需要确保将
my home directory to be the exact home
我的主目录更改为
directory I'm using. It's going to mount
我正在使用的确切主目录。 它会将该
that as a Docker volume. And look,
卷挂载为 Docker 卷。 你看，
cursor is like, let me help you out.
光标就像在说：“让我来帮你吧。”
Thank you, cursor. And then down here,
谢谢你，光标。 然后在这里，
you can notice that with the Docker MCP
您可以注意到，使用 Docker MCP
command, we can run more than one
命令，我们可以运行多个
catalog. And that's the secret sauce
目录。 这就是秘诀
here. We're referencing the main Docker
所在。 我们引用的是 Docker 主
catalog. And then also our custom one,
目录。 还有我们自定义的那个，
which I need to change that name because
我需要改一下名字，因为自
I did not name it custom. I named it my
定义并不是我起的名字。 我把它命名为我的
custom catalog.
自定义目录。
That should be it, I think. And then
我想应该就是这样了。 然后
notice we're referencing this registry
请注意，我们引用的是
that we already edited. And that should
我们已经编辑过的注册表。 这就是
be all we have to worry about. Going to
我们应该担心的全部了。 准备
save this file. And I'm going to launch
保存此文件。 我即将推出
Claude. Fingers crossed we get no
克劳德。 但愿不会
errors. Claude, don't disappoint me,
出错。 克劳德，别让我失望，
buddy. Here we go. You'll get a scary
兄弟。 开始了。 如果程序不接受，你会收到一个可怕的
error if it doesn't like it because it
错误信息，因为它会
tries to test the containers. So far so
尝试测试容器。 到目前为止，一切都
good. Click on my tools. Go down to my
很好。 点击我的工具。 请登录我的
MCP toolkit gateway and see if my tools
MCP 工具包网关，看看我的工具是否在
are there. Come on. Flip a coin. That
那里。 快点。 抛硬币。
looks nice. Oh, come on. Come on. Come
看起来不错。 哦，拜托。 快点。
on. Roll. There's all the stuff. There's
快点。 卷。 东西都在那儿。
all the tools. Cool. It's showing up.
工具都齐了。 凉爽的。 它出现了。
The MCP tools are available, but do they
MCP 工具虽然可用，但它们真的
work? Let's try it out. Now, the read me
有效吗？ 我们来试一试。 现在，自述
file gave me some options to say or try.
文件给了我一些可以尝试或说的选项。
Okay, let's roll a 2d6
好的，让
for me using the dice tool.
我们用骰子工具掷一个 2d6。
Come on. Come on. I will give you
快点。 快点。 我会给你
permission, buddy. You got this.
许可的，兄弟。 你一定可以的。
It worked. Yes. Oh, let's do something
成功了。 是的。 哦，我们来做点
simple like flip a coin using the dice
简单的，比如用骰子工具抛硬币
tool. Man, so cool. I can generate D and
。 哇，太酷了。 我可以生成D和
D stats. Let's try this.
D统计数据。 我们来试试这个。
I don't play D and D, so I don't know
我不玩龙与地下城，所以我不知道那是什么
what that means. Oh my gosh, what's it
意思。 我的天哪，它
even doing? Well, that's cool either
到底在干什么？ 不管怎样，这都很酷
way, which I have no idea what's
，虽然我不知道
happening, but it seems awesome. Okay,
发生了什么，但看起来很棒。 好了，
we got a simple MCP server out of the
我们已经搞定了一个简单的 MCP 服务器
way, but what about something that is a
，但是
bit more complex? For example, I use a
更复杂的服务器呢？ 例如，我使用一个
timer tool called toggle, which I use to
名为 toggle 的计时器工具，我用它来
track how much time I'm using to script
跟踪我编写脚本
and and film. So, for example, right now
和拍摄所花费的时间。 例如，
over here in my browser, I'm currently
我现在正在我的浏览器里
filming and I've been doing that for 51
拍摄，我已经拍摄了 51
minutes. Toggle has a great API, but no
分钟了。  Toggle 拥有很棒的 AP​​I，但没有
MCP server. I would like to use an MCP
MCP 服务器。 我想使用 MCP
server so I can chat with Claude or
服务器，这样我就可以和 Claude 或
whatever LLM I have and control my
我拥有的任何 LLM 聊天，并控制我的
timers or check in on my timers. Let's
计时器或查看我的计时器。 我们
do that right now. So, back here at the
现在就去做。 所以，回到
prompt, I just got to describe what I
题目这里，我只需要描述我
want.
想要什么。
I want to create a toggle MCP server.
我想创建一个切换 MCP 服务器。
This will
这将
use the toggle API. Now, I'm not going
使用切换 API。 现在，我不会一直坐在
to sit here and talk about this the
这里谈论这件事
entire time. You'll see what I write,
。 你会看到我写的内容，
but I'm having to make sure I answer all
但我必须确保回答
these questions here.
这里的所有问题。
All right, that's what I want. I want it
好的，这就是我想要的。 我希望它能
to do three things. Start a timer, stop
做到三件事。 启动计时器、停止
a timer, and view existing timers. And
计时器和查看现有计时器。
I'm just pasting the link to the toggle
我只是把切换
API documentation. Let's go find it.
API 文档的链接粘贴过来。 我们去找找吧。
Okay, it should be able to figure
好的，它应该能解决
everything out past that. All right,
剩下的所有问题。 好了，
Claude, new project for you. Go coffee
克劳德，给你安排个新项目。 你去喝杯咖啡，
break while I build this another MCP
我趁这段时间再搭建一台MCP
server.
服务器。
I also have it programmed to ask any
我还设置了程序，让它询问完成此任务所需的任何
questions that aren't answered that it
未解答的问题
task. Now, remember, when you're working
。 记住，在使用
with AI, it's all about context. If you
人工智能时，一切都取决于上下文。 如果你
provide it enough context, good context
提供足够的背景信息，
for what you want to do and you describe
为你想做的事情提供良好的背景信息，并且描述
it well, you're going to have amazing
得当，你将会获得惊人的
results. Okay, it finished. Same steps
结果。 好了，结束了。 步骤
as before with one minor difference. So,
与之前相同，只有一个细微差别。 所以，
I'll do my Docker file. So, I'll create
我要编写我的 Docker 文件。 所以，我会创建
a new directory, add in all the files.
一个新目录，把所有文件都添加进去。
All right. Now, I'll build that new
好的。 现在，我要搭建那台新
server.
服务器了。
This is so cool. And then I'll need to
太酷了！ 然后我需要
add my API key. Now, remember the cool
添加我的 API 密钥。 现在，请记住
thing about Docker MCP gateways, we can
Docker MCP 网关的一个很棒的功能，我们可以使用
manage our secrets with Docker.
Docker 管理我们的密钥。
Remember, I haven't told you that yet.
记住，我还没告诉你这件事呢。
The Docker MCP gateway, it can help you
Docker MCP 网关可以帮助您
manage your secrets, things like API
管理密钥，例如 API
keys and tokens. Keep that stuff out of
密钥和令牌。 请将这些信息从
your code and nestled safely inside
您的代码中移除，并安全地存储在
Docker MCP secrets. Anyways, back to me.
Docker MCP 密钥中。 好了，回到我身上。
Also, I explain more about Docker MCP
另外，我会在视频后面更详细地解释 Docker MCP
gateways later in the video. As I
网关。 正如我
mentioned before, you don't want to miss
之前提到的，你绝对不想错过
that part. So I'll do docker mcp secret
那一部分。 所以我会执行 docker mcp secret
list or ls rather to see what we have
list 或 ls 命令来查看我们有哪些密钥，
just our obsidian API key that we added
只有我们
earlier in the guey but we can do it
之前在 guey 中添加的 obsidian API 密钥，但我们也可以在
manually here as well. So I'll do docker
这里手动添加。 所以我会执行 docker
mcp secret and it's going to be set and
mcp secret 命令，它会被设置到
my toggle API token environment variable
我的切换 API 令牌环境变量中，
and then I'll add in my API key right
然后我现在就添加我的 API 密钥
now. Done. Secret set. Let's do ls once
。 完毕。 秘密场景。 我们再运行一​​次 ls 命令，
more to see if it's there. Yep, there it
看看它是否在那里。 没错，就在那儿
is. Now it's time for the catalog piece.
。 现在轮到产品目录部分了。
Now I could make a new catalog. You can
现在我可以制作一个新的产品目录了。 你可以多买
have a bunch or I can just add this to
一些，或者我可以把它添加到
my existing catalog to make it easy. And
我现有的目录中，这样更方便。
I think I'll just do that. So I'll grab
我想我就会这么做。 所以我
just the part I need, the toggle server
只需要获取我需要的部分，即切换服务器
itself describing all of its tools. And
本身及其所有工具的描述。
then edit my custom catalog
然后编辑我的自定义目录，
and add it right after dice. I think
并将其添加到骰子之后。 我觉得
it's all lined up. Awesome. Crl + XY
一切都安排妥当了。 惊人的。  Ctrl + XY
enter to save. And then we'll update our
回车保存。 然后我们会更新
registry. adding that tool right below
注册表。 把这个工具添加到
dice.
骰子下方。
[Applause]
[掌声]
Now, because that catalog is already in
现在，因为该目录已经在
our Claude configuration, we don't have
我们的 Claude 配置中了，所以我们不必
to worry about it. We'll just restart
担心了。 我们直接重启
Claude. And that should be all we have
克劳德。 这就是我们所需要的一切
to do. Fingers crossed. Here we go. I'm
。 但愿如此。 开始了。 我正在
doing this live. Like, what you saw was
直播。 就像你看到的都是
real. Everything past this point. No
真的。 此后的一切。 没有
errors. Oh my gosh, that's so good.
错误。 我的天哪，太棒了！
Okay, let's check our tools. The timer
好的，我们来检查一下工具。 计时器相关的
stuff might be at the bottom here. Ah,
内容可能在最底部。 啊，
there it is. Start, stop, view, timers.
找到了。 开始、停止、查看、计时器。
Oh, okay. So, currently I'm filming and
哦好的。 所以，我现在正在拍摄，
I have a timer for that. Do I have any
我设置了定时器。 我目前有任何
current timers right now? I'm not even
计时器吗？ 我甚至都不会
going to tell it what tool to use. Let
告诉它该用什么工具。 让它自己
it figure it out. Come on. Come on. Of
解决吧。 快点。 快点。
course, buddy. Here you go.
当然，哥们儿。 干得好。   是的
Yes, it's I almost spilled my coffee.
，我差点把咖啡洒了。
Oh, no. I did. But it worked. I got to
哦，不。 我做了。 但它奏效了。 我得把
clean this up.
这里清理干净。
You'd be surprised how often this
你会惊讶于这种情况
happens. Okay, now let's say um stop
发生的频率。 好的，现在我们来停止
that timer.
计时器。   它能
Can it do it? No, you didn't. It totally
做到吗？ 不，你没有。 确实如此
did. Okay, now restart it. Come on. Oh
。 好了，现在重新启动。 快点。
my gosh, it did. That's so cool.
我的天哪，真的发生了。 太酷了。
Isn't that just the most insanely
那是不是
powerful thing you've ever seen? You can
你见过的最不可思议的强大东西？ 你
do whatever you want. How about we build
想做什么都可以。 我们何不开发
a hacking MCP? Yes, I'm going to show
一个黑客MCP呢？ 是的，我
you how to build right now a Kali Linux
现在就向你展示如何构建一个 Kali Linux
hacking MCP. This one is interesting and
黑客 MCP。 这个很有意思，而且
we won't need any special uh API stuff.
我们不需要任何特殊的API之类的东西。
We're just going to run a Kali Linux
我们将运行一个 Kali Linux
container, which is actually supported
容器，它
now on a Mac. So, that's really cool.
现在实际上在 Mac 上也受支持。 那真是太酷了。
We're going to run it right here on our
我们将在本地机器上运行它
machine. And I've got a description here
。 我这里有一份
that I've used. Let's see how well this
我用过的描述。 让我们看看效果如何
does. Okay, that should give it a lot of
。 好的，这应该能提供很多
information. Let's throw it in there and
信息了。 把它放进去，
let it go to work. Now, it may kick back
让它发挥作用吧。 现在，它可能会对
on you because you're trying to build a
你造成反噬，因为你试图构建一个
hacking container, but if you frame it
黑客容器，但如果你以
the right way, it'll be fine usually.
正确的方式构建它，通常不会有问题。
Okay, I like that. Happy authorized
好的，我喜欢。 授权测试顺利进行
testing. It's done. Let's build it out.
。 完成了。 让我们把它建成。
Same story as before. for we'll create a
情况和之前一样。 因为我们将创建一个
new directory, create all our files,
新目录，创建所有文件，
build our container, which might take a
构建容器，这可能需要一些
moment. So, perfect time for I mean,
时间。 所以，现在正是时候，我的意思是，
well, you know, by this point. Tell you
嗯，你知道，到了这个地步。 告诉你吧
what, while you're sitting there, have
，既然你坐在这里，
you hacked the YouTube algorithm today?
你今天有没有破解 YouTube 的算法？
Let's make sure you do. Hit that like
我们一定要确保你做到。 点赞
button, subscribe, notification bell,
、订阅、开启通知、
comment. You got to hack YouTube today.
评论。 今天你得黑掉YouTube。   当然
Ethically, of course.
，这是从道德层面来说的。
Okay, that actually was pretty fast,
好吧，速度确实很快，
which makes me a little bit nervous, but
这让我有点紧张，但
we'll see how it goes.
我们看看结果如何吧。
right under our toggle server and edit
直接在我们的切换服务器下方编辑
our registry.
我们的注册表。   好了
All right, it's done. I really hope this
，完成了。 我真心希望这能
works. We're going to restart Claude.
奏效。 我们将重启克劳德项目。
No errors. No errors. Come on. Come on.
没有错误。 没有错误。 快点。 快点。
Okay, let's see if our Cali tools are in
好的，我们来看看 Cali 工具是否在
there. We should see some pretty crazy
里面。 我们应该会在里面看到一些非常疯狂的
stuff in there. If it's all working
东西。 如果一切运行
correctly. H, it's not there. What tools
正常的话。 哦，它不在那里。
am I looking for? There should be like
我需要哪些工具？ 应该有一个类似
an end mapap scan. Nothing. It hates me.
结束 mapap 扫描的命令。 没有什么。 它恨我。
Let's double check our work. Maybe it
让我们再检查一遍工作。 也许它
wants my secret set. That's why it's
想要我的秘密套装。 这就是它
failing.
失败的原因。
I feel good this time.
这次我感觉很好。   是的
Yes. Okay. I just wanted the secret set.
。 好的。 我只是想要那套秘密套装。
Okay, cool. Now, let's test some Kali
好的，明白了。 现在，让我们测试一下 Kali
Linux
Linux
scan on network 10.70.2.024.
在网络 10.70.2.024 上的扫描情况。
do a pretty quick one. Okay, we're
做一个简短的。 好的，
allowing the tool if this works. Oh my
如果这个工具有效，我们就允许使用它。 哦，我的
goodness. Oh, there's a white list. Did
天啊。 哦，这里有个白名单。
I put in a white list myself? Oh, yes.
我自己设置过白名单吗？ 哦是的。
Yes, yes, okay. Okay, it put in guard
好的，好的，没问题。 好的，
rails for me, Claude. Oh, all right.
克劳德，它为我安装了护栏。 哦，好的。
So dumb.
真蠢。
Remove the white list stuff. I want this
移除白名单相关内容。 我希望这里
wide open.
完全敞开。
put in guard rails
设置护栏也
can't stop me from hacking. Okay, I got
阻止不了我进行黑客攻击。 好的，我得到了我
it to give me what I what I needed. I
需要的东西。 我
think I'll have to adjust the Docker
想我得调整一下 Docker
file and the server. I'll just do them
文件和服务器。 我全都做一遍
all. Who knows what this LLM changed
。 谁知道这个法学硕士课程的修改
requirements is the same.
要求是否还一样。
Let's build it again. That should be it.
让我们重新建造它。 应该就是这样了。
I want restart Claude. Let's check our
我想重新开始克劳德的故事。 我们来检查一下
tools. Make sure they're there. There
工具。 确保他们在场。
they are. Okay. Again. Okay. Okay, I'm
它们就在那里。 好的。 再次。 好的。 好的，我
going to change it to make sure I'm
要修改一下，确保我
running as root. Okay, that should do
以 root 用户身份运行。 好了，应该可以了
it. Building again. Restarting Claude.
。 重新开始。 重启克劳德。
Come on. What the heck? Oh, the Docker
快点。 搞什么鬼？ 哦，原来是 Docker
file was screwing me up. Yeah, comment
文件把我搞砸了。 对，把
out the user.
用户注释掉。   就是这样。
That's what it was. This is so dumb.
这太蠢了。
Let's build it again.
让我们重新建造它。
All right, better work this time.
好吧，这次一定要好好表现。
It's driving me nuts.
这快把我逼疯了。
Let's do a Docker PS. See if it's
让我们来做 Docker PS。 看看它是否在
running. It's running, but it's only
运行。 它正在运行，但只有在
running while we're doing this. Kelly
我们这样做的时候才会运行。  Kelly
Linux is being used right now by an LLM,
Linux 目前正被一位法学硕士（LLM）和一位
by AI. I can talk to my hacking box with
人工智能（AI）使用。 我可以用简单的语言和我的黑客设备对话
plain language. Hey, go hack that thing.
。 嘿，去黑掉那个东西。   它确实做到了
And it does it. Now, while that's
。 现在，趁着它还在
scanning, I'm going to show you one I've
扫描，我要向你们展示一个我已经用和
methods we've used here so far. It's on
我们目前为止完全相同的方法构建出来的模型。 它在
my MacBook. I want to show you this one
我的MacBook上。 我想给你们看看这个，
because I've played with this one a lot.
因为我玩过很多次这个。
This will all be in the documentation
所有这些内容都将在
below. Got a few more tools here. Let's
下面的文档中列出。 这里还有一些工具。 我们来
try this. It's just so crazy. We can do
试试这个。 真是太疯狂了。 我们能做到
this. All right. Doing an end mapap
。 好的。 正在进行结束 mapap
scan. This is so awesome. I finished in
扫描。 太棒了！ 我在 endmap 中完成了，而
endmap not necto durb buster. And in
不是 necto durbuster。 如果
case you're wondering, you can use all
你好奇的话，你
these things with claw code as well.
也可以用 Claw 代码来实现所有这些功能。
This one I don't know what's going on
这个人我不知道
with him. He's taking forever.
他到底怎么了。 他磨蹭了半天。
So in case you're wondering, I'm using
所以，如果你好奇的话，我使用的是
the DVWA web app. An app that's
DVWA 网络应用程序。 一款
intentionally insecure so you can try
故意设计得不安全的应用程序，以便你可以尝试进行
and hack things. And there's a log of it
黑客攻击。
right here. Me hitting it. Oh, cool.
这里就有记录。 我击中它。 哦，真棒。
This one's working now. WordPress scan.
这个现在可以用了。  WordPress扫描。
WP scan. And dude, this thing's killing
WP扫描。 老兄，这玩意儿简直太棒了
it.
。
SQL map coming in. I'm like using AI to
SQL映射文件正在传输中。我现在正用人工智能
hack this from like three different
从三台不同的电脑上破解它
computers right now. This one finished.
。 完成了。
It found out what it was. Now, if you're
它查明了那是什么。 现在，如果你和
like me, you got to be wondering, how is
我一样，肯定会想知道
this all working? Like, are these MCP
这一切是如何运作的？ 这些MCP
servers actually running as Docker
服务器实际上是在Docker容器中运行的吗
containers? Are they running all the
？ 他们一直在跑吗
time? If I run Docker PS right now, am I
？ 如果我现在运行 Docker PS，我能
going to see containers running? No.
看到容器正在运行吗？ 不。
Then what's happening? And are all MCP
那到底是怎么回事？ 所有MCP
servers local like this? or are there
服务器都是像这样本地化的吗？ 或者是否存在
remote MCP servers? Let's talk about
远程MCP服务器？ 我们
that right now. We're about to get super
现在就来谈谈这件事。 我们要开始认真
nerdy. I hope you're ready for this.
钻研技术了。 希望你已经做好准备。
Let's dive in. Now, first thing I want
让我们深入了解一下。首先，我想向
to show you is that whenever we're
大家展示的是，当我们使用
here with Docker Desktop, it's running
Docker Desktop 与 MCP 服务器交互时，它会短暂运行
those MCP server containers
这些 MCP 服务器容器，
briefly and then taking them down. You
然后将其关闭。 你
want to see? Watch. Let's do this
想看吗？ 手表。 我们来执行这条
command. Hope it works on Mac. I haven't
命令。 希望它在Mac上也能运行。 我还没
tried this. do watch dash n0.5
试过。 执行 watch dash n0.5
docker ps
docker ps
brew install watch
brew install watch
dang.
dang。
All right, we'll just run it while we're
好的，我们就在做其他事的时候运行它
doing stuff. Let's use claude to call a
。 让我们用 claude 来调用一个
tool and we'll just spam docker ps. Use
工具，然后我们只需狂按 docker ps 命令。 使用
Airbnb tool to find a house in Tokyo for
Airbnb 工具在东京寻找一栋适合
a family of eight for two weeks starting
八口之家入住两周的房子，入住时间从
October. Let's get our command ready.
十月开始。 让我们准备好指挥部。
Allow once. Let's watch. Oh, wait. I
允许一次。 我们来看。 哦，等等。 我
wasn't ready. Ah, here we go.
还没准备好。 啊，开始了。   速度
It was too fast. I didn't catch it in
太快了。 我没能及时发现
time. We'll just use this watch command
。 我们在这里就使用这个 watch 命令
here or this while true loop. Ah,
或者这个 while true 循环。 啊，
perfect.
太好了。
Let's see if it shows up now. Ah, there
看看现在能不能显示出来。 啊，找到了
it is. We briefly caught it. It's so
。 我们短暂地捕捉到了它。 速度真
fast. That took longer than I thought it
快。 追踪此事比我想象的要花费更多时间
would be to track it. All that to say,
。 也就是说，
every time we engage with an MCP server,
每次我们与 MCP 服务器交互时，
a Docker container for the MCP server is
都会启动和关闭一个 MCP 服务器的 Docker 容器
spun up and spun down. They're not
。 它们不是
running all the time, only when we need
一直运行的，只在我们需要的时候才运行
them, which is kind of cool. But that's
，这挺酷的。 但这
only running an MCP server locally.
仅仅是在本地运行 MCP 服务器。
There's actually other ways to access
实际上还有其他方法可以访问
MCP servers, specifically remote MCP
MCP 服务器，特别是远程 MCP
servers. There's one from Coin Gecko,
服务器。  Coin Gecko 就是一个不错的选择，
which is a popular site we can use to
这是一个很受欢迎的网站，我们可以用来
find out the prices of cryptocurrency.
查询加密货币的价格。
So, we'll have this Coin Gecko MCP
例如，我们将使用 Coin Gecko MCP
server to cursor, for example. We'll go
服务器作为光标。 我们将进入
to our cursor settings and go to our MCP
光标设置，然后进入 MCP
and integrations config and we'll add a
和集成配置，并添加一个
new custom MCP server. And what it's
新的自定义 MCP 服务器。 它将
going to do is open up a MCP server
打开一个 MCP 服务器
file. And by the way, this is exactly
文件。 顺便说一句，
how most of the applications we use
我们使用的大多数应用程序的界面都长这样
look. In fact, watch. Look at Claude.
。 事实上，请观看。 看看克劳德。
This right here is Claude's config. I'll
这是克劳德的配置。 我也会用
open that in cursor too. And now you're
光标打开它。 现在你
not seeing double. These are two
不会再看到重影了。 这是两个
different uh config files, but it's a
不同的配置文件，但这是
standard, right? So they look the
标准做法，对吧？ 所以它们看起来
stinking same. But here for cursor, I'm
完全一样。 但是对于光标，我要
going to change this config. Adding coin
更改这个配置。 这里添加了硬币
gecko right here. Notice our Docker MCP
壁虎。 请注意，我们的 Docker MCP
server is running a command with the
服务器正在运行一个带有
Docker command and all these arguments.
Docker 命令和所有这些参数的命令。
We'll cover that in a second. But this
我们稍后会谈到这一点。 但
one here is actually just reaching out
这里实际上只是在连接
to an external URL. This is an external
到外部网址。 这是一个外部
MCP server. We're not hosting it.
MCP服务器。 我们不负责主办。
Someone else is. And it's using this
另一个人是。 它使用的是
transport SSE. We'll cover that here in
SSE 传输方式。 我们稍后会详细介绍
a moment. I'm going to save it. We'll
。 我要把它保存下来。 我们在
open up a new chat here and say, what is
这里开一个新的聊天窗口，问问大家：
the current price of XRP? Use the Coin
XRP 目前的价格是多少？ 使用 Coin
Gecko MCP server. We'll let it run the
Gecko MCP 服务器。 我们让它运行这个
tool. Let it get the sample price. And
工具。 让它获得样品价格。 就是这样。 这真是
there it is. So, that's super handy. But
太方便了。 但这让
this kind of drove me crazy. And if
我简直抓狂。 如果
you're like me, you probably thought the
你和我一样，你可能也这么想
same thing. Like, how is this
。 这种
communication working? What do MCP
沟通方式效果如何？  MCP
servers use for communication for
服务器使用什么进行
transport? Well, it depends on if you're
传输通信？ 这取决于你是在
running local or remote. The most
本地运行还是远程运行。 最让
interesting one that I'm like, how is
我感到好奇的是
this working was docker because we're
Docker，因为它能做到这一切
simply I mean this all this is doing.
。
It's configured to run the Docker
它配置为运行 Docker
command plus MCP gateway run. Like
命令以及 MCP 网关运行。
literally, the command will be like
字面上来说，命令会是这样的
this. I can probably run it right now.
。 我现在应该就能运行它。
Docker MCP gateway run. Like, yeah,
Docker MCP 网关运行。 没错，它
that's what it's doing. And look, it's
就是这么做的。 你看，它
actually running. and listing all those
真的在运行。 列出所有
tools and the server is now up. I'll
工具后，服务器现已启动。 我会
stop that. So, what's really interesting
阻止这种行为。 所以，真正有趣的
is every time you try to use an MCP
是，每次你尝试使用
server with Docker, it's actually going
Docker 运行 MCP 服务器时，它实际上都会先
to run the MCP gateway and then run the
运行 MCP 网关，然后再运行
specific MCP server. It's kind of crazy.
特定的 MCP 服务器。 这简直太疯狂了。
We'll cover that here in a second. I
我们稍后会详细介绍。 我
know I keep saying that, but again,
知道我一直在说这句话，但说
seriously though, if we're just running
真的，如果我们只是运行
commands, how is this working? What's
命令，这怎么可能有效呢？ 沟通内容是什么
the communication? It's actually just
？ 实际上，它只是
output via the command line. That's it.
通过命令行使用标准输出、标准输入和输出。 就是这样。
This is direct communication between
这是
local processes on the same machine.
同一台机器上本地进程之间的直接通信。
JSON RPC messages are exchanged through
JSON RPC 消息通过
pipes. Meaning the transport is almost
管道进行交换。 这意味着运输成本几乎
nothing. It's just like you sitting next
为零。 就像你坐在
to me and I go, "Hi." Like that's it.
我旁边，我跟你说“嗨”。 就这样。
There's no need to go over a network or
无需通过网络或
anything, which is fantastic because
其他任何东西，这太棒了，因为
there's like no latency, no network
几乎没有延迟，也没有网络
overhead. And you'll see that in
开销。 你会发现，在像
situations like this where we're running
这样的
Docker MCP servers locally. Now, you can
本地运行 Docker MCP 服务器的情况下，情况就是如此。 现在，
run MCP servers without Docker. Docker
无需 Docker 即可运行 MCP 服务器。  Docker
is just making it crazy easy for us. But
真的让一切变得无比简单。 但
most of the time when you're running on
大多数情况下，当你在
your local machine, you're going to be
本地计算机上运行时，你会
using standard input and output. But
使用标准输入和输出。 但如果
what about when it's remote, not on the
是远程操作，不在
same computer, not on the same network.
同一台电脑上，也不在同一网络上呢？
Well, we're going to be using HTTP. And
我们将使用HTTP协议。
in most cases, it should be HTTPS.
大多数情况下，应该使用 HTTPS。
And that's for client to server. It's
这是客户端到服务器之间的通信方式。 它将
going to be using SSE or server side
使用 SSE（服务器端
events, which is what we see right here
事件），这就是我们在这里看到的
as our transport for server to client.
服务器到客户端的传输方式。
And this is a lot more complex, right?
这要复杂得多，对吧？
Like you're setting up a web server at
就像你现在正在搭建一个网络服务器一样
this point. You're setting up
。 您正在设置
authentication. So operating a remote
身份验证。 所以，操作远程
MCP server is a whole thing. Whereas
MCP 服务器是一件大事。 而如果您在
Docker container on your local machine,
本地机器上的 Docker 容器中运行自己的 MCP 服务器，
you're just using standard input and
则只需使用标准输入和
output. All local, man. It's awesome.
输出即可。 都是本地产的，伙计。 太棒了。
But now, real quick, I want to talk
但是现在，我想快速谈谈
about this MCP gateway thing because
这个 MCP 网关，因为
it's a little crazy. And by crazy, I
它有点不可思议。 我说的“疯狂”是指“棒
mean awesome. Normally, you'd have to
极了”。 通常情况下，您需要
configure an MCP server like this, one
像这样逐个配置 MCP 服务器，
at a time, one service. So, we'd have
一次配置一个服务。 所以，我们可以在
multiple entries here for whatever
这里为任何
service we want. But we saw that in
我们想要的服务创建多个条目。 但是我们看到，在
Docker, we didn't add just one server to
Docker 中，我们并没有只在配置中添加一个服务器
our config, did we? We added a bunch.
，对吧？ 我们添加了很多。
Here's our list of servers right here.
以下是我们的服务器列表。
We have what, how many? six. Yet in our
我们有几？多少？ 六。 然而，在我们
MCP server list here in cursor, we have
这里显示的 MCP 服务器列表中，有
one MCP server set up with Docker.
一个 MCP 服务器是用 Docker 设置的。
That's the gateway. If I already use
那是入口。 如果我现在已经开始使用
some marketing speak right now, buckle
一些营销术语，请系好
your seat belts. The Docker MCP gateway
安全带。  Docker MCP 网关
through containerized MCP servers. What
通过容器化的 MCP 服务器提供安全、集中和可扩展的 AI 工具编排。
does that mean? It means when we have
这意味着什么？ 这意味着，当我们有
Claude or Cursor, our clients, we just
Claude 或 Cursor 这样的客户端时，我们只需将
connect them to one MCP server. We only
它们连接到一个 MCP 服务器即可。 我们只
need to manage one connection. And this
需要管理一个连接。 而通过这
one connection, this one MCP server
一个连接，通过这台 MCP 服务器，
gives us access to a lot of stuff, a lot
我们可以访问很多东西，很多
of other MCP servers. So, I don't know
其他的 MCP 服务器。 我不知道
about you, but it seems like this is a
你怎么想，但我觉得这个
lot cleaner than this. And of course,
比这个干净多了。 当然，
we'd also have to deal with all the
我们还要处理所有身份
authentication, the secrets for each
验证问题，以及
connection, for each client that
每个连接客户端的每次连接的密钥
connects. But not with Docker MCP
。 但 Docker MCP
gateway. It's all centralized right
网关则不然。 所有东西都集中在
there. Killer. I hope you're starting to
那里。 杀手。 希望你现在开始
see how cool this is. Or is it just me?
明白这有多酷了。 还是只有我这么觉得？
I don't know. Comment below if it's just
我不知道。 请在下方留言，告诉我只有
me or if you're joining me in this
我一个人这么觉得，还是你也和我一样
excitement. Hold on. I need some more
兴奋。 坚持，稍等。 我需要再喝点
coffee. I'll be right back. You can get
咖啡。 我马上回来。 你还可以再来点
some more coffee, too.
咖啡。
Okay, that's steaming, man. Check that
哇，这热气腾腾的，老兄。 看看这个
out.
。
Almost don't even need to drink it.
几乎都不需要喝。   是的
Yeah, I do. Now, let's get to the CLI
，我有。 现在，我们快速了解一下命令行界面 (CLI)
real quick. My favorite place in the
。 我最喜欢的地方
entire world. Let's go. You saw that we
。 我们走吧。 您已经看到我们
have some new commands with Docker.
为 Docker 添加了一些新命令。
Things like Docker MCP gateway. We just
例如 Docker MCP 网关。 我们刚才
tried that out. Our LLM app is actually
试过了。 我们的LLM应用程序实际上
going to run that command for us or we
会为我们运行该命令，或者我们也
can run this manually. We don't really
可以手动运行它。
need to unless we want it to be accessed
除非我们希望
remotely. We can actually do this.
远程访问，否则我们其实不需要这样做。 我们完全可以做到。
We can specify the transport to be
我们可以将传输方式指定为
standard input output SSE streaming to
标准输入输出 SSE 流，
make it available over the network. I
使其可以通过网络访问。 我
know right. Imagine running your own
知道，对吧。 想象一下，您可以为家庭网络或企业中的所有设备运行自己的
Docker MCP gateway server for all the
Docker MCP 网关服务器
business. just okay we're on the same
。 好的，我们达成共识了
page here. I think we also have the
。 我认为我们还有
docker mcp catalog command which we can
docker mcp catalog 命令，我们可以
look at our if we do ls we can see we
查看一下。如果我们执行 ls 命令，可以看到我们
have our default docker mcp catalog and
有默认的 docker mcp 目录，而且
there is an official way where you can
还有官方的方法可以
create your own docker mcp server and
创建自己的 docker mcp 服务器，并将
submit that to be added to the official
其提交到官方
catalog. You can do that but you have to
目录中。 你可以这样做，但必须
get it approved. You have to wait and
获得批准。 你得等，但
I'm not very patient. I don't know about
我没多少耐心。 我不知道
you. Docker actually does help us manage
你怎么想。  Docker确实能帮助我们管理
our secrets. So Dr. MCP secrets. Now
密钥。 所以，MCP博士的秘密。
what's a secret? What are you talking
什么是秘密？ 你在说什么
about? Things like API keys, ooth. You
？ 比如 API 密钥、OOT 之类的东西。 您
can securely manage your secrets with
可以使用 Docker 安全地管理您的密钥
Docker. Now, two more crazy things I
。 现在，我还要给你们展示两件更疯狂的事情
want to show you. Right now, we're
。 目前，我们正在使用
running Docker MCP gateway with Docker
Docker Desktop 运行 Docker MCP 网关
Desktop. That's like the official way to
。 目前来说，这算是官方的官方做法，
do it right now because they have the
因为他们有
MCP gateway in beta that you can run
MCP 网关的测试版，可以和
alongside of it. But if you check out
它一起运行。 但如果你查看一下
the documentation, and I bet they're
文档，我敢肯定他们会把
going to make it better and better and
它做得越来越好，
better and better. Dude, this coffee is
越来越好。 老兄，这咖啡劲儿太大了，感觉
like hitting me like crazy. I love it.
像中了毒一样。 我喜欢它。
I'll put this link below, but you can
我会在下面放上这个链接，但你可以将
run the Docker MCP gateway as a Docker
Docker MCP 网关作为 Docker
container totally apart from the Docker
容器运行，完全独立于 Docker
MCP toolkit and Docker Desktop. Been
MCP 工具包和 Docker Desktop。 最近一直在
saying Docker a lot. Coffee break. Which
说Docker。 咖啡休息时间。 这
means yes, you could run a headless
意味着，是的，你可以在其他地方运行一个无头
server somewhere else running all kinds
服务器，运行各种各样
of crazy stuff. And I'm going to show
疯狂的东西。 接下来我
you this real quick. I'm going to run
快速地给你们演示一下。 我将运行
the gateway Docker MCP gateway run
网关 Docker MCP 网关运行
transport. I'm going run it with SSE. I
传输。 我打算用SSE指令集运行它。 我
think that's how we do it. Yes. So now
想我们就是这么做的。 是的。 所以现在
it's actually running over the network
它实际上是通过网络运行，
instead of standard input output. It's
而不是通过标准输入输出运行。 它运行在
on port 8811. That's my IP address. So,
8811 端口上。那是我的 IP 地址。 那么，
real quick, I'm going to jump into NAN,
我马上要快速地进入 NAN，
my local NAN configuration here in my
这是我工作室里的本地 NAN 配置
studio. This is going to be so powerful.
。 这将非常强大。
I'll create a new workflow. I'll have an
我将创建一个新的工作流程。 我会派一个
AI agent come in and do something crazy.
人工智能代理进来做些疯狂的事。
And I'll give it a tool. How about an
我会给它提供一个工具。
MCP server? I think it'll just be HTTP
MCP服务器怎么样？ 我想应该就是HTTP协议加上
slash the IP address port 8811.
IP地址和8811端口。
Let's see.
我们看看。
Oh, it sees everything. Yes. Look at
哦，它什么都看得见。 是的。 瞧瞧
that. Over the stinking network. Okay.
。 通过这个臭气熏天的网络。 好的。
Okay. So, let's um I'm too excited. I'm
好的。 嗯……我太兴奋了。 我
so sorry. Let's give it a crazy prompt.
很抱歉。 让我们给它一个疯狂的提示。
Okay. Three steps. Find the best
好的。 三个步骤。 找到最好的
restaurant and Airbnb next to it and
餐厅和它附近的 Airbnb，
then put it in my Obsidian vault using
然后使用三种不同的工具将它们放入我的 Obsidian 保险库中
three different tools. Can it do it? I
。 它能做到吗？ 我
have no idea. Let's see. I'm so excited
不知道。 让我们来看看。 我非常兴奋，想
to see if this works.
看看这是否有效。
Something broke, though.
不过，某个部件坏了。
How to tell to ignore robots. See if
如何告诉机器人忽略你。 看看是否
it'll be okay. Oh, yeah. Yeah, it's
可行。 哦，是的。 是的，
great. Yes.
太棒了。 是的。   请
Look at the logs here in the terminal.
查看终端中的日志。
It using all these things, all these
它用到了所有这些东西、所有这些
tools, but I forgot step three. Oh, I
工具，但我忘记了第三步。 哦，我
didn't give it memory. Hold on. You know
没有给它分配内存。 坚持，稍等。 你知道
what? Let's try to oneshot this.
吗？ 我们试试一次性搞定。   我们
Let's go. This is magic. This is pure
走吧。 这是魔法。 这简直
magic.
太神奇了。
You did it. There it is. All right. So,
你做到了。 找到了。 好的。 那么，
where's the best restaurant? Okay. So,
哪家餐厅最好呢？ 好的。 所以，
it gave me a lot of options. Needs some
它给了我很多选择。
work on the prompt, but still, it used
提示信息还需要改进，但即便如此，它仍然能够
all the tools just like that over the
通过网络使用所有工具
network. And it was with one command I
。 我只用了一个命令就
did, right? Like that wasn't that hard.
做到了，对吧？ 好像这并不难似的。
Okay, you just learned MCP. Not only can
好了，你刚刚学会了MCP。 你不仅可以
you use an MCP server, but you learned
使用 MCP 服务器，而且你还学会了
how to build one yourself and you know
如何自己搭建一个服务器，并且你知道
how it works. That's a skill. Put that
它是如何工作的。 那是一种技能。 把这个写进
on your stinking resume. Who do you know
你那份糟糕的简历里。 你认识谁会
that knows how to do this? The list is
做这件事吗？
not very long right now. Now, I would
目前名单并不长。 现在，我
love to know what you thought of this
很想知道您对这段
video and what you plan on building with
视频的看法，以及您计划使用
MCP servers. Please comment below and
MCP 服务器构建什么。 请在下方留言
let me know. Also, if you like more
告诉我。 另外，如果你喜欢更多
stuff like this, more AI automation,
类似的东西，更多人工智能自动化，
which is like more real world, right?
这更贴近现实世界，对吧？   也
Check out my other video on N8N, an
请看看我关于 N8N 的另一个视频，
automation platform that's just
这是一个令人叹为观止的自动化平台
mind-boggling. That video was so fun to
。 制作那个视频真的很有趣，
make and I plan to make another one on
我打算在此基础上再制作一个
top of that. And of course, you saw how
。 当然，您也看到了
I connected our MCP environment, the
我是如何将我们的 MCP 环境、
Docker MCP gateway to N8N, opening up
Docker MCP 网关连接到 N8N 的，这开启了
just a billion possibilities. It's
无数的可能性。 这
endless. We're in a gold rush
没完没了。 我们
opportunity right now just to learn and
现在正处于一个学习、
create and do things like crazy. Don't
创造和疯狂尝试的淘金热时期。 别
waste it. That's all I got. I'll catch
浪费了。 我掌握的就这些。 下次再见！